PAULINA LE

• Full-Stack Developer •

EXPERIENCE

SEI TEACHING ASSISTANT

General Assembly | Jan 2022 - present

- Leads 1-to-1 debugging with students and reviews software development concepts taught each unit
- Supports 30+ software engineering students outside of class on daily deliverables and monthly projects
- Communicates regularly with instructional team on progress and needs of each student

SOFTWARE ENGINEER FELLOW

General Assembly | Oct 2021 - Jan 2022

- 12-weeks software development and programming immersive with 500 hours of extensive training
- Built and deployed 4+ functioning full-stack, front-end, and back-end applications implementing 7+ frameworks and programming languages
- Collaborated with fellow developers to execute products, as well as routinely debugging, wireframing, and testing

HEALTH FITNESS SPECIALIST

Corporate Fitness Works | Feb 2019 - present

- Assists in managing 3 DOJ fitness centers and completing monthly BOD reports
- Creates and leads 25+ safe, effective group exercises classes and videos per month

PROJECTS

NETFLIXIFY | MERN STACK

DEPLOYED APP

Software Engineer | Jan 2022

- Individually engineered a full-stack application for users to create customized Netflix playlists
- Implemented the unogsNG and uNoGS APIs to allow users to search over 17000 Netflix videos across over 35 countries

DEVXCHANGE | MERN STACK

DEPLOYED APP

Git Manager & Software Engineer | Dec 2021

- Collaborated with two developers to create an open forum application to connect developers and engineers of all expertise levels
- Maintained the state of two repos by handling and merging incoming pull requests appropriately frameworks and programming languages

HEAVY THINGS TRACKER | PEN STACK

DEPLOYED APP

Software Engineer | Nov 2021

- Independently designed and built a full-stack CRUD application where users can save exercises and log details on completed workouts
- Utilized two external APIs to allow users to search over 1300 exercises and upload workout photos

CONTACT

- **(**) 703-577-6528
- paulinal3@outlook.com
- in linkedin.com/in/paulinal3
- github.com/paulinal3

PROFILE

I am a full stack software developer who strives to provide efficient and functional products. I am passionate about using technology to create a healthy space for users. My previous experience as a personal trainer has given me a creative outlook on how to approach different challenges and the patience to find effective solutions.

SKILLS

- JavaScript/ES6
- HTML5
- CSS/Bootstrap
- React.js
- Node.js/Express
- Python
- MongoDB
- PostgreSQL
- Version Control

EDUCATION

Certificate - Software Engineering Immersive General Assembly Oct 2021 - Jan 2022

Bachelor of Science - Human Nutrition, Foods and Exercise Virginia Tech

Aug 2014 - May 2018